Guide to the New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NYCOSH) Records WAG.029
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Archived Websites, September 2007-ongoing; cuid8012; 4 websites in 4 archived websites.
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually. In 2020, the crawls were increased to monthly captures.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of https://nycosh.org/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  The collection was expanded to include th NYCOSH Twitter feed.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically by capture date.